Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VII: Health Project, undated, 1962-1980
  - Area III: Eastern Connecticut
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1737)
    - Health Service Area Profile, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1738)
    - Preliminary Application, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1739)
    - CCRG Testimony, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1740)
    - Organizational Activities (Box 44:, Folder 1741)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 44:, Folder 1742)
    - Peer-Group Appointment, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1743-1744)
    - Board of Directors (Box 44:, Folder 1745)
  - Area IV: North Central Connecticut
    - Preliminary Activities, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1746)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1747)
    - Incorporation and By-Laws, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1748)
    - CCRG Testimony (Box 44:, Folder 1749)
    - Application for Agency Designation, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1750-1751)
    - Organizational Information, 1975-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1752-1754)
    - UConn Health Center Study, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1755)
  - Area V: Northwestern Connecticut
    - Preliminary Activities (Box 44:, Folder 1756-1757)
    - Health Service Area Profile, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1758)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1759)
    - Health System Plan, 1975 (Box 45:, Folder 1760)
    - Health Planning Council Pamphlets, 1974-1975 (Box 45:, Folder 1761)
    - Application for Conditional Designation (Box 45:, Folder 1762)
    - Application for Agency Designation, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1763-1769)
    - CCRG Testimony, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1770)
    - Organizational Material, 1975-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1771-1772)
    - Consumer Review Panel, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1773)
  - Health Issues
    - CCRG: Health Action League (Box 45:, Folder 1774)
    - Commission on Hospitals and Health Care, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1775-1780)
    - Connecticut Health Bulletin, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 1781)
    - Drugs, 1962-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1782)
    - Eastern Regional Mental Health Board, 1978-79 (Box 45:, Folder 1783)
    - Emergency Medical Services, 1973-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1784)
    - Environmental Action Bulletin, 1974 (Box 45:, Folder 1785)
    - Health Care Costs, 1974-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1786)
    - Health Care Industry, 1975 (Box 45:, Folder 1787)
    - Health Care Occupations, 1970-75 (Box 45:, Folder 1788-1790)
    - Health Dictionary, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1791)
    - Health Insurance Notes, 1974-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1792)
    - Health Insurance Statutes and Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 45:, Folder 1793)
    - Health Insurance Pamphlets, 1975-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1794)
    - Health Law Project, U. Of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 45:, Folder 1795-1798)
    - Health Law Project, U. Of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 46:, Folder 1799-1805)
    - Health Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1806)
    - Health Dictionary, CCRG: Copyright Information, 1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1807)
    - Health Information, 1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1808)
    - Hill-Burton: Newsletters, 1976-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 1809)
    - Hospitals: Mt. Sinai and Hartford, 1975-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1810)
    - Hospitals: Notes, Report, Federal Register, 1973-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1811)
    - Indian Health Service (Box 46:, Folder 1812)
    - Lead Poisoning Testimony, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 1813)
    - Letters of Support (Box 46:, Folder 1814)
    - Low Cost Health Care, 1972-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1815)
    - Low Income Planning Aid, 1976-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 1816)
    - Malpractice (Box 46:, Folder 1817)
    - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 46:, Folder 1818)
    - Mental Health (Box 46:, Folder 1819)
    - New Horizons: Organization for Physically Handicapped, 1973-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1820)
    - Newark, New Jersey, 1972 (Box 46:, Folder 1821)
    - Nursing Homes, 1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1822-1823)
    - Orthomolecular Psychiatry: Articles, Pamphlets, 1968-1974 (Box 47:, Folder 1824)
    - Orthomolecular Psychiatry: Articles, 1968-1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1825)
    - Physicians (Box 47:, Folder 1826-1827)
    - Position Paper (Box 47:, Folder 1828)
    - Professional Standards Review (Box 47:, Folder 1829)
    - Public Citizen, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 1830)
    - Public Health and Safety Committee (Box 47:, Folder 1831)
    - Questionnaire (Box 47:, Folder 1832)
    - Releases (Box 47:, Folder 1833)
    - Review and Comment (Box 47:, Folder 1834)
    - Rothchild, Joel (Box 47:, Folder 1835)
    - Southeastern Citizen Action Group, 1978 (Box 47:, Folder 1836-1837)
  - Health and Environment
    - Air Pollution, 1973-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1838)
    - Campbell, Axel: Radiation Sickness Case, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1839)
    - Carter Administration: Environmental Prognosis, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1840)
    - CCAG, 1973-1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1841-1843)
    - CEPED, 1976-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1844-1846)
    - Citizen Participation, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1847)
    - Civil Penalties, Connecticut, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 1848)
    - Commission on Environmental Protection, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1849)
    - Costle, Douglas: Notes, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1850)
    - Council on Environmental Quality, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1851)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1976 (Box 47:, Folder 1852)
    - Environment/Economic Issues, 1972-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1853-1857)
    - Environment and Energy Publications, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 1858)
    - Environment/Unemployment, 1970-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1859-1860)
    - Environmental Protection agency: Publications, 1973-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1861)
    - Food and Nutrition: Publications, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1862)
    - Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 47:, Folder 1863)
    - Murphy, Betty: Dental x-ray Case, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1864)
    - Natural Resources, 1976-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1865)
    - New England Consortium, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1866)
    - New England Regional Commission Conference, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1867-1868)
    - Oil and Gas: News clippings, 1975-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1869)
    - Oil Refineries, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1870)
    - Oil Spills: Notes and Research News, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1871-1872)
    - Olympic Games: Environmental Impact Statement, 1980 (Box 47:, Folder 1873)
    - "Quits and Fires" Controversy, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1874)
    - Sewers: Town News, 1976-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1875)
    - Solid Waste: News clippings, 1976 (Box 47:, Folder 1876)
    - State and Urban Development, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1877)
    - J.P. Stevens: AFL-CIO News, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1878)
    - J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1978 (Box 47:, Folder 1879)
    - Town Environmental Issues: News clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 47:, Folder 1880)
    - U.S. Army Corps, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1881)
  - unspecified
    For further information, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files and Miles Rappoport Files; Series III: Administrative Files; Series X: Mary Mushinky Files; and Series XVI: Subject Files.
- Series VIII: North Haven Mall, undated, 1978-1984
  - Addressing the Record of Decision (Box 48:, Folder 1882)
  - Air Pollution Report (Box 48:, Folder 1883)
  - Appeal for Interrogatories (Box 48:, Folder 1884)
  - Arguments Against (Box 48:, Folder 1885-1886)
  - Army Corps of Engineers Record of Decision (Box 48:, Folder 1887)
  - Army Corps of Engineers Report (Box 48:, Folder 1888)
  - Army Corps of Engineers Pressures (Box 48:, Folder 1889-1890)
  - Automobile Dealers Association (Box 48:, Folder 1891)
  - Back Files (Box 48:, Folder 1892)
  - Bishop Street Project (Box 48:, Folder 1893)
  - Buckland Commons (Box 48:, Folder 1894)
  - Bus System (Box 48:, Folder 1895)
  - Campaign for Human Development (Box 48:, Folder 1896-1897)
  - Census Tracts (Box 48:, Folder 1898)
  - Citizens for the Environment (Box 48:, Folder 1899)
  - Civil Court Summons (Box 48:, Folder 1900)
  - Clean Air Act (Box 48:, Folder 1901)
  - Cluster Captain's Meeting (Box 48:, Folder 1902)
  - Code of Ethics (Box 48:, Folder 1903)
  - Congressman Bruce Morrison (Box 48:, Folder 1904)
  - CCAG Reports (Box 48:, Folder 1905)
  - CCAG/STM (Stop the Mall) Membership Meeting (Box 48:, Folder 1906)
  - Citizen/Labor Energy Coalition (CLEC) (Box 48:, Folder 1907)
  - CT State Implementation Plan (Box 48:, Folder 1908)
  - CT Valley Geologic and Hydrologic Studies (Box 48:, Folder 1909)
  - Danbury (Box 48:, Folder 1910)
  - Department of Transportation Hearing (Box 48:, Folder 1911)
  - Economic Development (Box 48:, Folder 1912)
  - Energy Input Study (Box 48:, Folder 1913)
  - Evidence of Other Malls (Box 48:, Folder 1914)
  - Final Outline of Environmental Impact (Box 48:, Folder 1915)
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement (Box 48:, Folder 1916-1922)
  - Flood Insurance Study (Box 49:, Folder 1923)
  - Government Responses (DEP) (Box 49:, Folder 1924)
  - House of Representative Hearing (Box 49:, Folder 1925)
  - House Subcommittee Evidence (Box 49:, Folder 1926-1927)
  - International Downtown Executives Association (IDEA) (Box 49:, Folder 1928)
  - Legal Tools for Stop the Mall (Box 49:, Folder 1929-1930)
  - Lobby Day, 1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1931)
  - Local Hearing and Debate (Box 49:, Folder 1932-1933)
  - Mall
    - Advocates (Box 49:, Folder 1934)
    - Contracts (Box 49:, Folder 1935-1938)
    - Opponents (Box 49:, Folder 1939)
    - Pollution (Box 49:, Folder 1940)
    - Reports, 1983 (Box 49:, Folder 1941)
  - Malls in General (Box 49:, Folder 1942)
  - News from...STM/CCAG (Box 49:, Folder 1943)
  - North Haven Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 49:, Folder 1944)
  - North Haven Canvassing, 1980 (Box 49:, Folder 1945-1846)
  - North Haven Petitions (Box 49:, Folder 1947)
  - Northeast Utilities Press (Box 49:, Folder 1948)
  - Plan of Development (Box 49:, Folder 1949)
  - Planning Process, 1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1950)
  - Press Clippings (Box 49:, Folder 1951)
  - Public Hearing Transcript (Box 49:, Folder 1952)
  - Raffles, CCAG, 1980-1984 (Box 49:, Folder 1953)
  - Regionalism in S. Central Connecticut (Box 49:, Folder 1954)
  - Research Documents (Box 50:, Folder 1955)
  - Senior Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1956)
  - Spring Flooding (Box 50:, Folder 1957)
  - Stamford, 1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1958)
  - Stamford CAG, 1982-1983 (Box 50:, Folder 1959)
  - Statewide Leadership Council (SLC), 1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1960)
  - SLC Meeting, 1983 (Box 50:, Folder 1961)
  - Stop the Mall
    - General, 1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1962)
    - Address List (Box 50:, Folder 1963)
    - Consultants (Box 50:, Folder 1964)
    - Information (Box 50:, Folder 1965-1967)
    - Lists (Box 50:, Folder 1968)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50:, Folder 1969-1970)
    - Press Releases (Box 50:, Folder 1971)
    - Reports (Box 50:, Folder 1972-1973)
    - Squad Sheets (Box 50:, Folder 1974)
  - Testimony to Army Corps of Engineers (Box 50:, Folder 1975)
  - Traffic (Box 50:, Folder 1976-1978)
  - Transportation Improvement Plan (Box 50:, Folder 1979)
  - U.S. Catholic Conference, 1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1980)
  - Valley CAG (Box 50:, Folder 1981)
  - Waterbury CAG, 1980-1981 (Box 50:, Folder 1982-1986)
  - Westfarms Survey (Box 51:, Folder 1987)
  - Westfarms Mall Drainage (Box 51:, Folder 1988)
  - Westfarms Mall Taxes (Box 51:, Folder 1989)
  - West Region Administration, 1981 (Box 51:, Folder 1990)
  - Zone Amendment Opponents (Box 51:, Folder 1991)
  - Zone Change (Box 51:, Folder 1992)
- Series IX: Bottle Bill, undated, 1969-1978
  - Action Research Model, 1974 (Box 52:, Folder 1993)
  - Alcoholic Beverages Statistics, 1972-1974 (Box 52:, Folder 1994)
  - Background Report on the Colchester Regional Landfill, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1995)
  - Beer Prices, 1973-1975 (Box 52:, Folder 1996)
  - Book/Calendar Orders (Box 52:, Folder 1997)
  - Bottle Bill: Articles, Summaries, U.S. and Outside U.S., National, 1970-1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1998-2005)
  - Breweries, 1973-1974 (Box 52:, Folder 2006)
  - Brewers, 1972-1974 (Box 52:, Folder 2007)
  - Brewers Almanac, 1973 (Box 52:, Folder 2008)
  - Bureau of Domestic Commerce: Staff Study, 1975 (Box 52:, Folder 2009)
  - California, 1974 (Box 52:, Folder 2010)
  - California Senate Bill 650, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 2011)
  - Campaign for a Cleaner Environment: Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box 52:, Folder 2012)
  - Colorado, 1973-1974 (Box 52:, Folder 2013)
  - Committee Findings and Staff Papers on National Beverage Deposits, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 2014)
  - Connecticut Bottle Bill, 1973-1978 (Box 52:, Folder 2015-2017)
  - CCAG Correspondence, Memoranda, Surveys, Reports, Testimony, 1973-1976 (Box 52:, Folder 2018-2020)
  - Connecticut Legislators, 1975-1977 (Box 52:, Folder 2021)
  - Connecticut Legislative Sessions, 1973-1976 (Box 52:, Folder 2022-2024)
  - Connecticut Malted Beverage Shipments, 1973 (Box 52:, Folder 2025)
  - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, 1977-1978 (Box 52:, Folder 2026)
  - Connecticut Solid Waste Management Advisory Council, 1977-1978 (Box 52:, Folder 2027)
  - Crusades For A Cleaner Environment, 1975 (Box 52:, Folder 2028)
  - "Economics of Resource Recovery from Mixed Municipal Wastes" (Box 52:, Folder 2029)
  - "Energy and Economic Impacts of Mandatory Deposits", 1975 (Box 52:, Folder 2030)
  - Energy Bottles (Box 52:, Folder 2031)
  - Energy Consumption, 1972-1974 (Box 53:, Folder 2032-2033)
  - Environmental Action Foundation, 1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2034)
  - Environmental Groups, 1975-1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2035)
  - Environmental Impact of Nitrile, 1973 (Box 53:, Folder 2036)
  - "Environmental Barrier Containers" (Box 53:, Folder 2037)
  - "The Environment and Packaging: An Economic and Legislative Analysis", 1972 (Box 53:, Folder 2038)
  - Federal Energy Administration Study, 1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2039)
  - Federal Hearings: Solid Waste (Box 53:, Folder 2040)
  - "53,000,000 - - CT Resources Recovery Authority Greater Bridgeport System Bonds, Series A", 1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2041)
  - Humanities Conference on Bottle Bill, 1974-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2042)
  - Illinois (Box 53:, Folder 2043)
  - "Impact of Beverage Container Legislation on Connecticut", 1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2044)
  - Industry: Recycling, 1971-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2045-2047)
  - Industry: Testimony, 1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2048-2049)
  - Interested Citizens, 1974-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2050)
  - Legislative Headcounts, 1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2051)
  - Litter and Pricing Survey, 1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2052)
  - Maine Times, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 2053)
  - Maine, 1973-75 (Box 53:, Folder 2054)
  - Management and Behavioral Science Center, 1971 (Box 53:, Folder 2055)
  - Maryland, 1974-1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2056-2057)
  - Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 53:, Folder 2058-2059)
  - Midwest Research Institute, 1971 (Box 53:, Folder 2060)
  - Minnesota, 1974 (Box 53:, Folder 2061)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 53:, Folder 2062)
  - National Bottle Bill, 1972-1973 & 1975-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2063)
  - New England Economic Indicators, 1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2064)
  - New Hampshire, 1974-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2065)
  - New York State, 1973-1975 (Box 54:, Folder 2066)
  - Notes: High School Survey (Box 54:, Folder 2067)
  - Oregon, 1971-1977 (Box 54:, Folder 2068-2083)
  - Other States, 1973-1974 (Box 54:, Folder 2084)
  - "Packaging in Perspective", 1974 (Box 54:, Folder 2085)
  - "Potential Effects of a National Mandatory Deposit on Beverage Containers: Plastic Bottles, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 54:, Folder 2086)
  - Report of Model Litter Control Program, 1971 (Box 54:, Folder 2088)
  - "Resource Conservation and Recovery Act", 1976 (Box 54:, Folder 2089)
  - Resource and Environmental Profile Analysis, 1974 (Box 54:, Folder 2090)
  - Resource and Environmental Profile Analysis of Nine Beverage Container Alternatives, 1974 (Box 54:, Folder 2091)
  - "Resource Recovery From Municipal Wastes", 1972 (Box 55:, Folder 2092)
  - Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 55:, Folder 2093)
  - Schaefer Brewing Company, 1974 (Box 55:, Folder 2094)
  - Scientific Resources, Inc., 1973 (Box 55:, Folder 2095)
  - Solid Waste, 1969-1978 (Box 55:, Folder 2096-2099)
  - South Dakota, 1974 (Box 55:, Folder 2100)
  - Stern, Carlos, 1973-1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2101-2103)
  - Stowe Profiles (Box 55:, Folder 2104)
  - System Energy and Recycling: A Study of The Beverage Industry, 1972 (Box 55:, Folder 2105)
  - Verdieck, Emma: Correspondence and Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 55:, Folder 2106)
  - Vermont, 1972-1975 (Box 55:, Folder 2107-2114)
  - Virginia, 1975 (Box 55:, Folder 2115-2116)
  - Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 55:, Folder 2117)
  - Washington State, 1971-1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2118-2123)
  - Wisconsin, 1975 (Box 55:, Folder 2124-2125)
  - U.S. Brewer's Association, Inc. (Box 55:, Folder 2126)
  - U.S. Senate Hearings, 1974 (Box 55:, Folder 2127)
  - Abstentions for Bottle Bill, 1977 (Box 56:, Folder 2128)
  - Aluminum Containers (Box 56:, Folder 2129)
  - Amendments to HB5409, 1975 (Box 56:, Folder 2130)
  - America Can Rebuttal (Box 56:, Folder 2131)
  - Audubon: Connecticut (Box 56:, Folder 2132)
  - Beck Amendment, 1977 (Box 56:, Folder 2133)
  - Berkshire-Litchfield Environmental Council (Box 56:, Folder 2134)
  - Beverage Containers: Report (Box 56:, Folder 2135)
  - Bottles and Cans (Box 56:, Folder 2136)
  - Bottle Washing (Box 56:, Folder 2137-2139)
  - California Litter Tax (Box 56:, Folder 2140)
  - Cans (Box 56:, Folder 2141)
  - Connecticut Bottle Bill
    - Anti-Bill (Box 56:, Folder 2142)
    - Articles (Box 56:, Folder 2143)
    - Bill, 7977 (Box 56:, Folder 2144)
    - Bill, 7978 (Box 56:, Folder 2145)
    - Bill Efforts (Box 56:, Folder 2146-2147)
    - Coalition `78 (Box 56:, Folder 2148)
    - Energy Argument (Box 56:, Folder 2149)
    - Fact Sheet (Box 56:, Folder 2150)
    - Jobs Argument (Box 56:, Folder 2151)
    - Litter (Box 56:, Folder 2152)
    - Maine Inc.: Summary (Box 56:, Folder 2153)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 56:, Folder 2154)
    - Natural Resources (Box 56:, Folder 2155)
    - Paste-Ups (Box 56:, Folder 2156)
    - Petitions and Votes (Box 56:, Folder 2157)
    - Price Argument (Box 56:, Folder 2158)
    - Price Survey (Box 56:, Folder 2159)
    - Pro-Bill Industries (Box 56:, Folder 2160)
    - Procedures, 1977 (Box 56:, Folder 2161)
    - Projects for Students (Box 56:, Folder 2162)
    - Public Support (Box 56:, Folder 2163)
    - Retail Stores (Box 56:, Folder 2164)
    - Return Rates (Box 56:, Folder 2165)
    - Slide Show (Box 56:, Folder 2166)
    - Summary of Pro-Arguments (Box 56:, Folder 2167)
    - Votes, 1978 (Box 56:, Folder 2168)
  - CCAG Efforts, 1977 (Box 56:, Folder 2169-2171)
  - Connecticut Council on Environmental Quality (Box 57:, Folder 2172)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous (Box 57:, Folder 2173)
  - Conservation Commissions (Box 57:, Folder 2174)
  - Consumers, General (Box 57:, Folder 2175)
  - Crusade for a Cleaner Environment (Box 57:, Folder 2176)
  - Dayville Memorandum: Projected Job Losses (Box 57:, Folder 2177)
  - Deadline Dates: EPA, Departments of Interior and Commerce (Box 57:, Folder 2178)
  - Department of Environmental Protection: Legislation, Regulation, Personnel (Box 57:, Folder 2179-2182)
  - "Emma's Files" (Box 57:, Folder 2183)
  - EPA 4th Report to Congress (Box 57:, Folder 2184)
  - Energy Consumption of Beverage Containers (Box 57:, Folder 2185)
  - Environmental
    - Action (Box 57:, Folder 2186)
    - Caucus (Box 57:, Folder 2187)
    - Education (Box 57:, Folder 2188)
    - Groups, 1975 (Box 57:, Folder 2189)
    - Impact of Nitrile Barrier Containers (Box 57:, Folder 2190)
  - Federal Bill (Box 57:, Folder 2191)
  - Federal Guidelines (Box 57:, Folder 2192)
  - Federal Studies (Box 57:, Folder 2193)
  - Glass (Box 57:, Folder 2194)
  - House Abstentions, 1977 (Box 57:, Folder 2195)
  - House Debate Transcript, 1977 April 13 (Box 57:, Folder 2196)
  - House Debate Transcript, 1977 June 4 (Box 57:, Folder 2197)
  - Hull's (Box 57:, Folder 2198)
  - Information Packet (Box 57:, Folder 2199)
  - Jobs: Pinsky (Box 57:, Folder 2200)
  - Joint Press Release: LWV-CCAG (Box 57:, Folder 2201)
  - Legislative Session (Box 57:, Folder 2202)
  - Letter to Bottle Bill Supporters, 1978 (Box 58:, Folder 2203)
  - Litter (Box 58:, Folder 2204-2207)
  - Malt Beverage Shipments in Connecticut, 1969-1972 (Box 58:, Folder 2208)
  - Massachusetts Bottle Bill (Box 58:, Folder 2209)
  - Michigan (Box 58:, Folder 2210)
  - Miscellaneous Groups (Box 58:, Folder 2211)
  - National Coalition on Solid Waste (Box 58:, Folder 2212)
  - National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA) (Box 58:, Folder 2213)
  - Oregon Bottle Bill (Box 58:, Folder 2214-2216)
  - Other States (Box 58:, Folder 2217)
  - Pamphlets (Box 58:, Folder 2218)
  - Pennsylvania Alliance for Returnables (Box 58:, Folder 2219)
  - Plastic Bottles: Monsanto (Box 58:, Folder 2220)
  - Recycling Metal (Box 58:, Folder 2221)
  - Recycling (Box 58:, Folder 2222)
  - Redemption Centers (Box 58:, Folder 2223)
  - Report: Impact of Mandatory Deposit Legislation in CT (Box 58:, Folder 2224)
  - Returnable Bottles (Box 58:, Folder 2225)
  - Sales Survey of Soft Drink Industry, 1974 (Box 58:, Folder 2226)
  - Senate Vote, 1977 May 5 (Box 58:, Folder 2227)
  - Senator Martin Bottle Bill (Box 58:, Folder 2228)
  - Soft Drink Industry: State Profiles, 1973 (Box 58:, Folder 2229)
  - State Bottle Bill Fights: General (Box 58:, Folder 2230)
  - Tufts' Environmental Network (Box 58:, Folder 2231)
  - Tufts' Urban Environment (Box 58:, Folder 2232)
  - Vermont Bottle Bill (Box 58:, Folder 2233)
  - Washington Bill (Box 58:, Folder 2234)
  - Water Pollution Control Handbook (Box 58:, Folder 2235)
  - Wildlife (Box 58:, Folder 2236)
  - Wetland Seminar (Box 58:, Folder 2237)
  - unspecified
    For further information on this subject, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files; Series XI: Environmental Issues; Series XIV: Consumer Issues; and Series XVII: 1992 Addendum.
- Series X: Mary Mushinsky Files, undated, 1973-1979
  - Area Waste Treatment Management Board, 1977-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2238)
  - Asbestos, 1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2239)
  - Budget, 1977 (Box 59:, Folder 2240)
  - Citizens Lobby Membership Form, 1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2241)
  - Complaints, 1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2242)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2243-2246)
  - District Meetings, 1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2247-2252)
  - East Hartford Citizens Action Group (Box 59:, Folder 2253)
  - Environmental Action Group, 1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2254-2255)
  - Environmental Action Group (Folder 2 of 2), 1978-79 (Box 59:, Folder 2255)
  - Flyers and Pamphlets, 1977-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2257)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2257)
  - Garbage Coalition Hit Lists, 1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2258)
  - Granby: Whispering Pines, 1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2259)
  - Industrial Waste Management and Recovery Task Force, 1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2260-2261)
  - Madison Zoning Case, 1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2262)
  - Malls (Box 59:, Folder 2263)
  - Maps (Box 59:, Folder 2264)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 59:, Folder 2265)
  - Newsletters, 1974,1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2266)
  - North Haven, 1974 (Box 60:, Folder 2267)
  - North Haven CAG, 1974 (Box 60:, Folder 2268)
  - Norwalk Community College Case (Box 60:, Folder 2269)
  - Notes on Bills, 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2270)
  - Occupational Health, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2271)
  - Pinsky Studies, 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2272)
  - Planning Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2273-2275)
  - Press and Public Relations (Box 60:, Folder 2276)
  - Rate Hike Information, 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2277)
  - Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2278-2280)
  - Solid Waste Ballots, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2281)
  - Solid Waste Coalition Conference, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2282)
  - Stamford: Sewage Treatment Plant, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 2283)
  - Stamford Cemetery: Horner, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 2284)
  - State Ethics Commission, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 2285)
  - Steering Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2286)